[
	{
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: あ?",
		"answers": ["a"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: い?",
		"answers": ["i"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: う?",
		"answers": ["u"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: え?",
		"answers": ["e"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: お?",
		"answers": ["o"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: か?",
		"answers": ["ka"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: き?",
		"answers": ["ki"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: く?",
		"answers": ["ku"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: け?",
		"answers": ["ke"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: こ?",
		"answers": ["ko"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: さ?",
		"answers": ["sa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: し?",
		"answers": ["shi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: す?",
		"answers": ["su"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: せ?",
		"answers": ["se"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: そ?",
		"answers": ["so"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: た?",
		"answers": ["ta"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ち?",
		"answers": ["chi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: つ?",
		"answers": ["tsu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: て?",
		"answers": ["te"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: と?",
		"answers": ["to"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: な?",
		"answers": ["na"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: に?",
		"answers": ["ni"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ぬ?",
		"answers": ["nu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ね?",
		"answers": ["ne"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: の?",
		"answers": ["no"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: は?",
		"answers": ["ha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ひ?",
		"answers": ["hi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ふ?",
		"answers": ["fu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: へ?",
		"answers": ["he"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ほ?",
		"answers": ["ho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ま?",
		"answers": ["ma"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: み?",
		"answers": ["mi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: む?",
		"answers": ["mu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: め?",
		"answers": ["me"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: も?",
		"answers": ["mo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: や?",
		"answers": ["ya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ゆ?",
		"answers": ["yu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: よ?",
		"answers": ["yo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ら?",
		"answers": ["ra"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: り?",
		"answers": ["ri"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: る?",
		"answers": ["ru"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: れ?",
		"answers": ["re"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ろ?",
		"answers": ["ro"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: わ?",
		"answers": ["wa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: を?",
		"answers": ["wo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic hiragana is this: ん?",
		"answers": ["n"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: が?",
		"answers": ["ga"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぎ?",
		"answers": ["gi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぐ?",
		"answers": ["gu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: げ?",
		"answers": ["ge"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ご?",
		"answers": ["go"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ざ?",
		"answers": ["za"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: じ?",
		"answers": ["ji"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ず?",
		"answers": ["zu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぜ?",
		"answers": ["ze"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぞ?",
		"answers": ["zo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: だ?",
		"answers": ["da"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぢ?",
		"answers": ["ji"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: づ?",
		"answers": ["zu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: で?",
		"answers": ["de"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ど?",
		"answers": ["do"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ば?",
		"answers": ["ba"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: び?",
		"answers": ["bi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぶ?",
		"answers": ["bu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: べ?",
		"answers": ["be"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぼ?",
		"answers": ["bo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぱ?",
		"answers": ["pa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぴ?",
		"answers": ["pi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぷ?",
		"answers": ["pu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぺ?",
		"answers": ["pe"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced hiragana is this: ぽ?",
		"answers": ["po"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: きゃ?",
		"answers": ["kya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: きゅ?",
		"answers": ["kyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: きょ?",
		"answers": ["kyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: しゃ?",
		"answers": ["sha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: しゅ?",
		"answers": ["shu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: しょ?",
		"answers": ["sho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ちゃ?",
		"answers": ["cha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ちゅ?",
		"answers": ["chu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ちょ?",
		"answers": ["cho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: にゃ?",
		"answers": ["nya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: にゅ?",
		"answers": ["nyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: にょ?",
		"answers": ["nyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ひゃ?",
		"answers": ["hya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ひゅ?",
		"answers": ["hyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ひょ?",
		"answers": ["hyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: みゃ?",
		"answers": ["mya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: みゅ?",
		"answers": ["myu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: みょ?",
		"answers": ["myo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: りゃ?",
		"answers": ["rya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: りゅ?",
		"answers": ["ryu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: りょ?",
		"answers": ["ryo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぎゃ?",
		"answers": ["gya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぎゅ?",
		"answers": ["gyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぎょ?",
		"answers": ["gyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: じゃ?",
		"answers": ["ja"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: じゅ?",
		"answers": ["ju"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: じょ?",
		"answers": ["jo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: びゃ?",
		"answers": ["bya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: びゅ?",
		"answers": ["byu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: びょ?",
		"answers": ["byo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぴゃ?",
		"answers": ["pya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぴゅ?",
		"answers": ["pyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo hiragana is this: ぴょ?",
		"answers": ["pyo"]
    }
]